How dare you evil lowlifes ruin Hinamizawa's peace!
（梨花(りか)）
雛見沢(ひなみざわ)の平和を乱す悪人どもめ
Release Satoko immediately!
ボクの沙都子(さとこ)を離すのです！
Rika, don't come any closer!
（沙都子）
梨花 来ないでくださいまし
（北条(ほうじょう)）ハハハ
何 生意気抜かしてんねん
What's with that gaudy appearance, you slut?
この だらず！
It's pointless missy.
（小此木(おこのぎ)）
お前のような お嬢ちゃんが
我ら四天王に勝てると思うんかい
Do you think you can defeat us, the Four Lords?
（鷹野(たかの)）ウフフフッ
After this nobody will be able to to stop us no matter what crimes we commit.
（鷹野）
これまで何度も私たちの悪だくみを
邪魔してくれたけど…
Magical Girl Oyashiro Rika,
（野村(のむら)）魔法少女オヤシロリカ
your senseless struggle ends right now!
今日という日を
あなたの本当の命日にしてあげます
（北条）ヌハハハ
（小此木）おりゃあ！
（鷹野）はあっ！
（梨花）しまった！
Oh no!
夢？
A dream?
（梨花）私 成長したら
ああなるのかしら
I was grown... and had "those."
Rika, Rika, please run away!
（沙都子）梨花 梨花
逃げてくださいな
早く 早く！ うっ ハア ハア
Hurry, hurry!
んん～
（梨花）沙都子 沙都子
Satoko, Satoko!
Rika?
梨花？ はっ！
無事でしたのね よかった！
I'm glad you're alright!
It's okay now.
もう大丈夫なのですよ
あっ もしかして 沙都子も―
Don't tell me, you had a dream about me becoming a magical girl?
ボクが魔法少女になった夢を
見ていたのですか？
あっ… 夢？
A dream?
あっ 昨日 梨花が
祭具殿から持ってきた杖ですわね
Yesterday, you brought that staff home from the shrine's storage shed.
It seems to emit a strange aura.
“見覚えがないから”って
（梨花）そうなのです
Is that so?
I find it odd that there was a tool in there that I was unaware of.
ボクが知らない道具が
祭具殿にあるのは不思議なのです
I'm pretty sure the staff had
something to do with that weird dream.
きっと
こんなものを置いておいたから―
おかしな夢を見たんですわ
But, both of us having the same dream is really strange.
でも ２人で同じ夢を見るのは
変なのです
What could it mean?
一体 何が…
This is such a thick fog.
すごい霧ですわね こんなの
雛見沢では初めてですことよ
I've never seen a fog like this in Hinamizawa before.
Something strange is going on.
なんだか様子がおかしいのです
沙都子 気をつけるのです
Satoko, be careful!
So you've come!
（男性）現れたな
（梨花）あっ
Furude Rika!
（男性）古手(ふるで)梨花！ ウヘヘヘ…
な… 何者ですの!?
What in the world are you?!
Behold!
（男性）いでよ
祭具魔人ツメハガシャー
Ritual Tool Demon, Tsumehagasha!
（ツメハガシャー）
ツメハガッシャー
Happy! Lucky! Dochy! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Happy! Lucky! Dochy! No! No! No!
There is something that I want to tell you about
A secret conversation between the two of us, okay?
Then again, hold it, I'd rather not hear it
Because I'm afraid of scary stories
You're always terrified on the way back
So let's use some magic then
We take a detour and run away towards our secret hideaway
It's quite easy, very, very, easy!
Let's go!
In an instant, we've become happy and lucky
One!
Two!
Three!
I'm gonna let you have a peek at a maiden's heart!
Happy!
Lucky!
Receive my smile with a throbbing feeling
One!
Two!
Three!
Maybe so... whatever, which is it then?
Happy!
Lucky!
You see, the answer is that I
like
you
a
lot!
Happy!
Lucky!
Dochy!
Yes!
Happy! Lucky! Dochy! No! No! No!
Happy! Lucky! Dochy! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Specter Battling Chapter
ColorMeSubbed
～ Effort ～
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
Is this the continuation of that dream?
これって夢の続きですの？
I don't get it at all!
ボクにも訳が分からないのですう！
（男性）
んっ 逃げ足の速いやつらめ
Those brats are quick on their feet.
（鷹野）まさか
こうも あっさり逃げるとはねえ
Don't tell me they escaped you so easily?
Do not worry.
（男性）ご安心を
The 2nd and 3rd stages of the plan are already prepared.
我々には 第２ 第３の作戦が
準備してございます
Furude Rika.
（鷹野）古手梨花 これ以上
我ら東京マギカの邪魔はさせないわ
We, the Tokyo Magica cannot allow you to continue to interfere with us.
Prepare yourself.
覚悟しておいでなさい
フフフ…
What the heck was that about?
何だったんですの？ さっきのは
まるで怪獣映画ですわ
It was like something from a monster movie.
Satoko!
（詩音(しおん)）沙都子ー！
（詩音）おはようございます
（沙都子）うわあ！ ううっ…
Good morning!
You're cute today as usual!
今日も かわいいですねえ
（沙都子）うう あっ あっ
あっ もちろん
梨花ちゃまも かわいいですよ
Of course, Rika-chama is also cute.
Shi, why are you here?
詩ぃ なぜここにいるのです？
詩ぃが通っている学校は
この世界では…
If this is your school then this world must be...
（沙都子）んっ もう！
What about this world?
この世界って何のことです？
もちろん私の学校はここですよ
This is definitely my school.
Shi-chan you're so unfair!
（レナ）
詩ぃちゃんばっかり ずるーい
私も一緒に お持ち帰り～
I want to take her home right now!
（沙都子）ああ！
（悟史(さとし)）あっ おはよう
Ah, good morning!
Satoko, everybody.
（悟史）沙都子 みんな
（沙都子）あっ にーにー!?
Nii-nii?
Ganging up on Satoko already?
（圭一(けいいち)）
朝っぱらから沙都子いじりか？
お前らも飽きねえな
You sure are easygoing.
Of course.
無論です 沙都子も悟史君も
私にとっては大事な人ですから
Both Satoko and Satoshi-kun are very special people to me.
Nii-nii...
Nii-nii!
Huh?
Let me go!
離してくださいな
にーにーが帰ってきたんですのよ
Can't you see Nii-nii is back?
Calm down Satoko.
落ち着くのです 沙都子
（沙都子）あっ
That's probably not the Satoshi you know.
あれはたぶん 沙都子の知っている
悟史ではないのです
Eh?
Self Study
知恵(ちえ)先生 遅いですね
Chie-sensei is really late.
I'll look around the school for her.
僕 ちょっとその辺まで
様子を見に行ってくるよ
I'll come with you, to make sure you don't get lost in the fog.
俺も付き合うぜ もしかしたら
霧で迷ってるのかもしれない
ありがとう 圭一
Thanks, Keiichi.
No need to thank me, Satoshi.
（圭一）いいってことよ 悟史
（悟史）ハハッ
悟史と圭一が親しげなのです
何げに新鮮なのです
Satoshi and Keichi seem awful close.
It's just like they're old buddies.
Apparently they became close after he left our house due to family circumstances.
わたくしと にーにーは
家の事情で―
よそに預けられてることに
なってるみたいですわ
私は梨花の家に
にーにーは圭一さんの家に
I stayed at Rika's house, while Nii-nii stayed at Keiichi-san's.
雛見沢症候群のことも
東京との戦いも誰も覚えていない
No one remembers the Hinamizawa Syndrome or our battle with the people from Tokyo,
…といって
時間が戻ったわけではないようです
but we've not gone back in time.
Study
Monday
September 5th
Month
We've probably wandered into a parallel world.
おそらくボクたちは―
パラレルワールドに
迷い込んでしまったのです
A parallel world?
パラレルワールド？
梨花 よく落ち着いてられますわね
Rika, how can you be so calm?
わたくし 頭がどうかしそうですわ
All this is driving me crazy!
Mii~ That's because I've been through this before.
みぃ ボクは慣れているのです
（沙都子）えっ？
パラレルワールドの１つや２つ
今さら どうってことないのです
A parallel world or two is no big deal.
Nipaa~
にぱ～
But I'm concerned about that monster from before.
（梨花）ただ 気になるのは
さっきの怪物のことだわ
And Hanyuu's not around, what is going on...?
羽入(はにゅう)の姿も見えないし 一体…
（足音）
（圭一）た… 大変だあ！
It's an emergency!
They've appeared!
（圭一）やつらが出た
東京マギカの祭具魔人だ
Tokyo Magica's Ritual Tool Demon!
And they got Satoshi!
悟史がやられちまった
They got Nii-nii?
にーにーが!?
Tokyo... Magica?
東京マギカ？
（悟史）ハア… んっ…
Nii-nii! Nii-nii!
にーにー にーにー！
（詩音）悟史君！
Satoshi-kun!
Don't worry, he's gonna be fine.
（入江(いりえ)）心配しなくて大丈夫ですよ
見た目ほど大ケガじゃありません
Despite his state, he is going to be okay.
The monster suddenly appeared out of the fog.
霧の中から急に怪物が出てきたんだ
As we were about to flee, it got Satoshi...
逃げる間もなく悟史は…
んっ！
（梨花）怪物？
A monster?
（魅音(みおん)）
さては またやつらの仕業だね！
Then it really is their doing again!
間違いないでしょう
東京マギカが―
There's no doubt this is the work of Tokyo Magica.
They're using Ritual Tool Demons to attack people.
祭具魔人を使って
人々を襲わせているんです
Hold on, I wanna know something.
ちょっと待ってほしいのです
東京マギカって何のことなのです？
Who is Tokyo Magica?
What do you mean Rika-chan?
（魅音）
何言ってんの？ 梨花ちゃん
まさか寝ぼけてんの？
Are you daydreaming?
悟史君を
こんな目に遭わせたのは―
To leave Satoshi in this condition,
it has to be that secret magic-using society,
魔法を操る悪の秘密結社
東京マギカ！
Tokyo Magica!
（ハニュ）ウフッ ハニュ！
Hanyuu~
And Rika is the one who fights their demons.
そして 梨花は
彼ら あやかしの者と戦う戦士
You're a magical girl! Hanyuu~
魔法少女なのですよ ハニュ
I am Magical Girl Oyashiro Rika's adviser,
ボクは 魔法少女オヤシロリカの
アドバイザー
Hanyuu at your service! Hanyuu~
ハニュなのです ハニュ
（圭一）
すると 君たちは他の世界から来た
梨花ちゃんと沙都子なのか
So you're saying that Rika-chan and Satoko are from another world?
I can easily tell, since I'm Furude Shrine's deity! Hanyuu~
ボクには すぐに分かったのです
ボクは古手神社の神ですからハニュ
Then that means the two girls from this world are now in the other world?
すると こちらの世界の２人は―
入れ違いに向こうの世界に
行ってしまったんでしょうか？
もしかして
これも東京マギカの仕業なんじゃ…
Could this also be Tokyo Magica's doing?
（ハニュ）違うと思うのです
That's highly unlikely.
Tokyo Magica isn't strong enough to do that. Hanyuu~
いくら東京マギカでも
こんな力はないのですハニュ
Mii~ Tell me more about Tokyo Magica.
その東京マギカについて
教えてほしいのです
Those guys did this to Nii-nii?!
にーにーをこんな目に遭わせたのも
そいつらなのですわね！
Yes.
はい 初めから説明するのです
ハニュ
I'll explain from the beginning. Hanyuu~
Our Rika was originally Furude Shrine's priestess.
梨花はもともと 古手神社の巫女(みこ)
She was also in charge of the shrine's storage shed where ritual tools were stored. Hanyuu~
神社の祭具殿には 古い拷問器具が
しまわれていたのですハニュ
That's the same as in our world.
（梨花）それは
ボクたちの世界と同じなのです
Those tools have a lot of history behind them.
（ハニュ）
長い年月を経るうちに―
Because of that history, they possess immense power which others desire.
拷問器具にこもった怨念が増大し
大きな力を持ったのです
And the ones who plotted to steal them,
それを奪おうとしたのが―
is the secret society that manipulates black magic to their own ends, Tokyo Magica! Hanyuu~
魔法を操る悪の結社
東京マギカですハニュ
（北条）ヘッヘッヘ…
魔法を操る悪の結社
東京マギカですハニュ
祭具殿に押し入った彼らを
止めるべく―
To defend the storage shed, I gave Rika a magical staff. Hanyuu~
ボクは 梨花に魔法のステッキを
与えたのですハニュ
But we never expected them to wield such power,
（ハニュ）ところがハニュ
わずかに力及ばず…
（ハニュ）飛び散った拷問器具は
モンスターになり―
they ended up taking the tools,
and attacked the village with the Ritual Tool Demons! Hanyuu~
祭具魔人として
暴れだしたのですハニュ
Tokyo Magica is trying to turn the Ritual Tool Demons into magical weapons! Hanyuu~
東京マギカは祭具魔人を操って―
魔法兵器を
作ろうとしていますハニュ
Their goal is to use black magic to change the world
彼らの最終目的は―
この世界を暗黒の魔法で染め上げ
闇の世界を作ること
and build a new one bathed in darkness!
その第一歩として この雛見沢を
魔法兵器の実験場とし―
They plan to test their magical weapons first on Hinamizawa
and once they've drained Furude Shrine entirely,
更に 古手神社に残された―
they'll finally have acquired all the magical energy they desire! Hanyuu~
魔力をも奪おうとしているのです
ハニュ！ ハア…
（ハニュ）政府や警察にも すでに
彼らの仲間が入り込んでいるのです
The government and even the police are already on their side.
You're the only one who can protect Hinamizawa now, Rika! Hanyuu!~
雛見沢を守れるのは 梨花
あなただけなのですハニュ
The rest of us can't remain idle now that we know you're a magical girl.
梨花ちゃんが魔法少女だって
知ってるのは―
ここにいるメンバーだけなんだ
Games are not the only thing our club does.
ゲームに興じる部活とは仮の姿
The truth is, we stand together against Tokyo Magica as the Rika Support Squad!
実は 力を合わせて
東京マギカに立ち向かう―
梨花ちゃん応援団なのさ
And I'll be your supervisor.
そして 私は
監督のようなことをしています
ちなみに
隊員服は私がデザインしました
By the way, I've already designed outfits for everyone.
I've ended up in a completely crazy world this time.
よりにもよって
とんでもない世界に…
But somehow, this is the same way it would be handled in my Hinamizawa...
でも 微妙にボクたちの雛見沢と
状況設定がかぶっているのです
I'll never forgive Tokyo Magica!
（沙都子）
許せませんわ 東京マギカ！
Even if it's a different world, for them to do this to Nii-nii...
たとえ違う世界だろうと
わたくしのにーにーをこんな目に！
（詩音）そのとおりです
悟史君の敵(かたき)を討ちましょ
That's right!
Let's avenge Satoshi!
Rika, where's your magic staff? Hanyuu~
梨花 魔法のステッキは
どこにあるのです？ ハニュ
Uh?
Would it have been better if you never came to this world?
お前らは
来なくてよかったんじゃないか？
It's not like that.
そうはまいりませんわ
No matter what, we can't just ignore
what's happening and not take action.
何もせず じっとしてるなんて
耐えられませんもの
Satoshi is with the Supervisor,
悟史君には監督がついています
so we will tag along to help guard both of you.
私たちは
梨花ちゃまと沙都子を守らないと
But, can this Rika from a different world transform? Can she?
でも よその世界の
梨花ちゃんでも―
ちゃんと
変身できるのかな？ かな？
とにかく今は―
In any case, right now our biggest
priority is to get the staff. Hanyuu~
ステッキを手に入れることが
第一なのですハニュ
（知恵）カレー
（引きずる音）
Curry...
Hanyuu?~
ハニュ？
Curry...
（知恵）カレー カレー
（引きずる音）
Curry...
（知恵）カレー
（引きずる音）
Curry...
（知恵）カレー カレー
（引きずる音）
Curry...
（知恵）カレー
私の手作りカレーを―
Have a taste of my homemade curry!
食べなさあい！
（知恵）カレー！
CURRY!!
Hold it right there!
（知恵）待ちなさい
Won't you have a taste of the curry I made?
私の作ったカレーが
食べられないと言うんですか!?
（梨花）ハア ハア…
沙都子！ 圭一！
みんな どこに行ったのです!?
Satoko!
Keii-Keii!
Where is everyone?
キャー！
ハア ハア ハア…
（ハニュ）ハニュー！
Curry!!
（知恵）カレー！
（梨花）あっ んっ！
（知恵）アハハ アハハ…
（梨花）うわあ や… やめるのです
Stop this please!!
（梨花）ハア ハア ハア…
（ハニュ）ハニュハニュ ハニュー
Hanyuu~
ハア 何とか
逃げ切れたようなのです
We managed to lose them somehow.
Tomitake and Oryuu are acting weird. Hanyuu~
富竹(とみたけ)とお魎(りょう)も
おかしくなっているのですハニュ
Hanyuu.
羽入
（ハニュ）ハニュ？
Hanyuu?~
You're supposed to be my adviser right?
あんた 私の
アドバイザーなんでしょ？
Can't you sense where Satoko and the others are?
沙都子たちが どこにいるか
探知できないの？
Even if you tell me to do so...
そう言われても…
Then again, did your personality change? Hauu~
…っていうか梨花
なんだか性格が変わっているのです
The me from before is a child, while the me right now is someone else.
あっちの私はこうなのよ
ここでの梨花は違うの？
The Rika I know is an honest person without any hidden malice and a good kid.
ボクの知っている梨花は
素直で裏表のない よい子なのです
She puts all she has into being a magical girl! Hanyuu~
魔法少女のお仕事も
一生懸命 頑張ってたのですハニュ
Geez, transformations and magical girl stuff...
“変身”とか“魔法少女”とか
そんな面倒なこと―
I'm surprised the me from this world managed to do all that crap without a single complaint.
何の疑問も抱かずに
よくやっていられるものね
But she's an amateur I guess, so be glad I'm here in her place.
そういう甘ちゃんだから 私と
選手交代しちゃったんじゃないの？
Hauuauauu~
Rika!
（沙都子）梨花！
Thank goodness you're alright.
（圭一）
お前たちは無事か よかった
Where's Mii and Shii?
魅ぃと詩ぃは どうしたのです？
Hauuauauu~
あぅ～！
裏表ありすぎなのですハニュ
She's really into this split personality thing! Hanyuu~
We got separated.
はぐれちゃったんだよ
村の人たちが襲いかかってきて
逃げてるうちに…
We scattered and ran towards here when the villagers attacked.
（梨花）うーん おそらく―
Most likely this fog is causing people to behave strangely.
この霧に人をおかしくさせる作用が
あるのです
The events back in our original world were different but,
（梨花）ボクらの世界でも―
ちょっと成り行きは違うけど
似たようなことがあったのです
there are still similarities.
Since Rika and Satoko are not native to this world, the fog apparently doesn't affect you. Hanyuu~
（ハニュ）梨花と沙都子は
よその世界の人間だから―
影響はないと思うのですハニュ
But still, we have to hurry.
でも急がないと…
There you are, Rika-chan!
来たね 梨花ちゃん
待ってたよ
We've been waiting.
（魅音）ああ…
（詩音）沙都子
Satoko, let me make you even cuter.
たっぷり かわいがってあげますよ
覚悟してくださいね
Prepare yourself!
（レナ）ハハハハ…
（ハニュ）ハニュ！
Rika-chan, Satoko-chan...
梨花ちゃん 沙都子ちゃん
２人まとめて お持ち帰り～
I can't stop myself from taking both of you home!
It's time to abandon all hope Rika-chan, Satoko...
往生際が悪いよ
梨花ちゃん 沙都子
You need to be punished...
罰を与える必要がありそうですね
Abundantly...
たっぷりと みっちりと
Completely...
I'll burn you with gasoline to purify you.
（レナ）ガソリンで焼いて
きれいにしてあげる
It'll be really pretty.
きっと きれいだろうねえ
I think they have gotten stronger.
このトリオの そろい踏みは
迫力があるのです
なんか もう
絶対勝てねえって気がするな
I get the feeling we can't beat them head-on.
Here they come!
来ますわ！
Now that's truly "me."
さっすが わたくし！
（圭一）うわあ…
この世界でも ちゃんと
トラップを準備していましたわ
Even in this world I prepared traps!
ハニュ あったのですハニュ！
Found it! Hanyuu~
So without this, Rika-chan can't transform?
（圭一）
つまり こいつがなければ―
梨花ちゃんは
変身できないってことだな
Keiichi-san!
圭一さん！
さっきから
おかしいと思っていたのです
For a while now I had a feeling something was strange about you.
So that's why the fog didn't affect you at all.
なぜ お前だけが
霧に影響されないのか
Quite perceptive of you.
察しがいいな
それはもちろん 俺が最初から
あの霧に影響されていたからさ！
Of course, that's because I was under
it's influence from the start!
さては さっき
にーにーにケガをさせたのも―
So then you were the one who hurt Nii-nii?
あなたですわね
That's right!
そうよ ムラムラと
誰かをぶん殴りたくなってな
I have a tendency to bludgeon people!
Oh boy.
This world's Keiichi also has the same quirks.
こちらの世界の圭一も
時々 詰めが甘いようね
Huh?
Satoshi
Sorry, Keiichi!
（悟史）
圭一 ごめん めーん！
Satoshi
Men!
Nii-nii!
沙都子 間に合ってよかった
Satoko... Glad I was able to make it.
Nii-nii!
にーにー！
（悟史）沙都子
Satoko.
No matter what world it is,
they're definitely siblings.
世界は違っても やっぱり兄妹(きょうだい)ね
It's not over yet!
このままじゃ終わらねえぞ
Come forth Ritual Tool Demon, Tsumehagasha!
いでよ 祭具魔人ツメハガシャー！
（ツメハガシャー）ツメハガッシャー
（圭一）いけ！
Get them!
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
You got us good earlier.
さっきは よくもやってくれたわね
But, it's game over for you now!
でも ゲームはこれからだよ
悟史君 私がせっかんしてあげます
Satoshi-kun, let me give you a world of pleasure!
（入江）沙都子ちゃーん
（ハニュ）ハニュ
Satoko-chan...
Please wear my new costume design!
新デザインのコスチュームを
着てくださーい
My curry is really delicious you know!
私のカレー おいしいですよ
Care to have a taste of my ohagi?!
私のおはぎも食べてよね
Satoko... Let's get along nicely!
沙都子 お兄ちゃんと仲よくしよう
Nii-nii has changed into a deranged brother!
（沙都子）
にーにーが危ないお兄ちゃんに！
When he took off the mask, the fog was able to affect him.
マスクを取ったせいで
霧の影響を受けたのです
やっぱり梨花が
変身するしかないのですハニュ
There's no other way except for you to transform, Rika! Hanyuu~
梨花なら きっとできますわ
I'm sure you can do it.
It may be in a different form, but it's still using a mysterious power to fight evil.
形は違っても 不思議な力で
悪と戦うというのは同じこと
From the start, you were already something like a magical girl.
もともと 魔法少女みたいなもの
なんですもの
Rika!
（ハニュ）梨花
（沙都子）梨花
Rika...
Geez, I guess there is no other way.
（梨花）やれやれ しかたないわね
煌(きらめ)け！ オヤシロにぱにパワー
クリスタル メイクアーップ
Sparkle! Oyashiro Nipa-Nipower!
☆
Crystal Make Up!
魔法少女オヤシロリカ！
☆
Magical Girl, Oyashiro Rika!
You looked like you were having a lot of fun. Hanyuu~
（ハニュ）
すごく楽しそうなのですハニュ
Maybe she actually enjoys this kind of thing.
（沙都子）本当は ああいうの
好きなんじゃありませんかしら
あっ …って
子供のまんまなのですう！
What?! I'm still a kid!
ああ なんで なんで！
Why? Why?
It seems she thought she would become an adult. Hanyuu~
（ハニュ）大人になれると
思ってたみたいですハニュ
She's been a kid all this time, so she's always dreamed of having a mature body.
ずっと子供だったから
成長した姿に憧れてたんですのね
ふびんですわ
How sad.
I'll just channel my frustration into beating Tokyo Magica to a pulp!
くう この怒りを東京マギカに
たたきつけてくれるのです
For the sake of the villagers whose hearts have been sullied by evil,
邪悪な心にとらわれた
雛見沢の住人たちよ
I shall now purify them of all evil influence!
心を清め
正しい道に立ち返るのです
Nii-nii!
Keiichi, you're all that's left!
圭一 残るはお前だけなのです
Crap!
くっ いけ！ ツメハガシャー
あの小娘をぎゃふんと言わせろ！
Go Tsumehagasha!
Get that pipsqueak!
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
ハガッシャー ハガッシャー
（梨花）
やあ！ ふっ！
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
ハガッシャー ハガッシャー
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
Ritual Tool
Demon
Tsumehagasha
（梨花）えいっ！
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
（圭一）何!?
What?!
Time to clear your heart of evil, Keiichi!
正しい心を取り戻すのです 圭一
ええいっ！
（圭一）ぎゃああ！
Nooo!
（沙都子）
圭一さんのお顔が元どおりに！
His face returned to normal.
フウ あっちの世界でも―
If it had been this easy in the other world, we wouldn't have had any problems.
これくらい簡単にいけば
楽勝だったのです
（鷹野）ウフフッ
さすがは雛見沢の女王様ねえ
As expected of Hinamizawa's queen!
（鷹野）ウフッ
（梨花）鷹野！
Takano!
（沙都子）やはり ここでも
黒幕はあなたでしたのね
I knew it, even here you're the source of evil!
I'm one of Tokyo Magica's Four Lords: Takano Miyo.
東京マギカ四天王 鷹野三四(みよ)
I shall deal with you myself.
私が自らお相手するわ とうっ！
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
ツメ ハガッシャー！
ハガッシャー！
（沙都子）うわあ！
（ハニュ）ハニュー！
（沙都子）わあ！
Hanyuu~
（ツメハガシャー）ツメハガッシャー
（梨花）ふっ！
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
さあ 今度はどうかしら
Well, what will you do now?
（沙都子･ハニュ）梨花！
Rika!
沙都子 来てはダメなのです
Satoko, stay there!
If we fight there, Keiichi and the others might get trampled.
（梨花）あそこで戦っては
圭一たちが踏み潰されてしまう
場所を移動しないと！
I must lure her somewhere else...
（ツメハガシャー）シャー
Takano, I will clear your heart of evil too!
鷹野 お前も
正義の心を取り戻すのです
ええい！
そんな攻撃 効かないわあ
An attack like that won't work on me!
私には“祖父が残した魔法理論を
実証する”という―
Since my grandfather left me his research notes on magic, my skills are stronger than yours.
崇高な使命があるのだから
Rika!
梨花！
（ハニュ）さすがは四天王
As expected from one of the Four Lords, at this rate Rika may lose. Hanyuu~
このままでは
梨花が危うしなのですハニュ
（ツメハガシャー）
うう… ハガッシャー！
（ハニュ）ハニュ ハニュ ハニュ…
Hanyu-Hanyu-Hanyuu~
Satoko!
沙都子！
うっ！
（沙都子）梨花！
Rika!
（ハニュ）ハニュ
（梨花）沙都子
Satoko, stay back!
来てはダメなのです
（ツメハガシャー）ハガッシャー
Starting today, I shall be the queen of Hinamizawa!
今日から雛見沢の女王は この私！
（沙都子）うっ！
（ハニュ）沙都子!?
Satoko!
梨花はやらせませんわ
I won't let you hurt Rika!
It's no good, Satoko.
ダメなのです 沙都子 早く逃げて
Please, run away...
Until now you've taken on our painful encounters alone, Rika.
（沙都子）
梨花はこれまで わたくしたちのために
つらい思いをしてきましたわ
Now it's my turn to protect you!
今度は
わたくしが梨花を守る番ですことよ
沙都子
Satoko...
In that case, why don't you perish together?
（鷹野）
ならば ２人とも始末するまで
ああ もっと力があれば…
If only I had more strength...
梨花や
にーにーたちを守れる力が…
The power to protect Rika and Nii-nii!
（ツメハガシャー）シャー
（沙都子）
オヤシロさま 力をくださいな
Oyashiro-sama, please give me power,
the power to protect Rika and everyone!
わたくしに
梨花や みんなを守れる力を！
I've been waiting for you to say that! Hanyuu~
その言葉を
待っていたのですハニュ
沙都子 その心が 今こそ
大いなる力となるのですハニュ
Satoko, prepare your heart to receive an overwhelming amount of power! Hanyuu~
んっ？ 何ですの？
What's this?
沙都子 変身するのです
Satoko, transform now!
わたくしが？
（ハニュ）早くするのです！
Me?
Hurry up!
（沙都子）わ… 分かりましたわ
Okay then!
轟(とどろ)け！ オヤシロにぱにパワー
クリスタル メイクアップ！
Roar! Oyashiro Nipa-Nipower!
☆
Crystal Make Up!
Magical Girl Trap Satoko!
☆
魔法少女トラップサトコ！
沙都子！
Satoko!
（圭一）梨花ちゃん 沙都子！
（梨花たち）んっ？
Rika-chan! Satoko!
（ハニュ）みんな！
Everybody!
正気に戻ったのですねハニュ
They're back to their normal selves! Hanyuu~
What's going on?
これって どういうこと？
My little sister's a magical girl too?!
僕の妹まで魔法少女に!?
理由なんか どうでもいいです
カッコいいですよ
The reason doesn't matter, it's pretty cool!
How cute, I wanna take you both home!
かぁいい お持ち帰りしたい～
Rika, let's get this right!
梨花 反撃開始でしてよ
Yes, of course!
はいなのです 沙都子！
Satoko!
んっ ひるむな ツメハガシャー！
Don't hesitate, Tsumehagasha!
はあーっ！
（ツメハガシャー）ウガア…
たあ！
あっ トラップ!? あっ！
A trap?
（沙都子･梨花）
セブンスエクスプロージョン！
07th  Explosion!
stsh  Explosion
catg  Kevowash
yarr  piratesk
lolo  ROFLMANO
stfu  fargotss
pita  arsholes
（ツメハガシャー）
ツメ… ハガッシャー…
（鷹野）
おじいちゃん ごめんなさ～…
Onii-chan I'm sorry!
フッ 鷹野三四
Takano Miyo, she was all talk, full of nothing but hot air.
大きな口をたたきながら
たわいもない
She was an embarrassment to the Four Lords.
四天王の面汚しが
Well, she was the weakest amongst us anyway.
しょせん彼女は我らの中では最弱
Next I'll move out the Yamainu's Corps.
次は山狗(やまいぬ)部隊を出動させますぜ
いんにゃ 次はわしが行ったる
No, it's my turn to act.
Satoko still doesn't know I'm one of the Four Lords.
沙都子は まだ
わしが四天王だと知らんけえね
フフフッ
あのだらずをしつけちゃる
That gaudy slut!
I'll strip her of everything!
全裸で熱湯風呂に沈めたるんじゃ
Everything is...
すべては…
Everything is for the sake of Tokyo Magica!
（小此木）
すべては東京マギカのために！
（北条）
わしら３人 力と心を１つにし…
We three shall teach them
the meaning of fear with our powers!
We'll definitely defeat Furude Rika!
（一同）
必ずや 古手梨花を倒してみせる
おう！
I guess with this, we've
protected Hinamizawa for now.
ボクたちは どうやら―
この雛見沢を守る使命を
帯びているようなのです
That's right.
そうですわね
世界は違っても雛見沢は雛見沢
Even if it's a different world, Hinamizawa is still Hinamizawa.
I want to do what we can.
わたくしたちのできる限りのことを
したいですわ
Of course, we'll help you out!
もちろん 俺たちも協力するぜ
今日は迷惑かけちゃったけど
次は絶対 挽回(ばんかい)してみせるからね
We had trouble today, but we'll do better next time!
I'm worried to be honest.
正直 僕は心配だ
Satoko as a magical girl and...
沙都子まで
魔法少女になってしまって…
It'll be fine.
大丈夫ですよ
どんな強敵が現れようと…
No matter what enemy may appear,
... we'll definitely beat them!
きっと勝てる！
そして 雛見沢を
守ることができるはずだよ
And protect Hinamizawa at the same time!
That's right!
（ハニュ）そうなのです
Hinamizawa's peace is resting on all our shoulders! Hanyuu~
雛見沢の平和は
みんなの肩にかかっているのです
ハニュ
Let's do our best, Rika!
頑張りましょうね 梨花
ええ 沙都子
Right, Satoko!
Is this really okay?
ほんとに これでいいのかしら？
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
You can barely catch up to me as you give chase
Over there?
Over here?
My heart's in an uproar while
daydreaming more than ever!
We gladly hold something dear that appears to be junk
Never think, not even once, Satoko don't ever let go
I'm looking forward to after school,
now today what
kind of match shall we have?
Whatever the game is, we'll bring our special costume along
and transform!
Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
You can barely catch up to me as you give chase
Over there?
Over here?
My heart's in an uproar while
daydreaming more than ever!
The key is trust itself!
Through an act of God, the troubles are gone now
With strength behind us, we shall fight
and go forth to achieve a miracle!
We may not notice that the future may be a bit bleak, but
today we will be able to choose the path around it
which nobody expects at all
Yes! Our Chance!
Ohohohohohoho!
Our Dreams!
Nipaa!~
The time to surpass ourselves has now begun